{
	"response_code": 0,
	"results": [
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the quality of oil when EBRO level is between 0-19%",
      "correct_answer": "Good quality (green light)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Bad quality (blue light)",
        "Wrong quality (red light)",
        "Bad quality (amber light, oil change advised)"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the quality of oil when EBRO level is between 20-24%",
      "correct_answer": "Bad quality (amber light, oil change advised)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Good quality (green light)",
        "Bad quality (red light)",
        "Good quality (no light, no need to change oil)"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the quality of oil when EBRO level is more than 24%",
      "correct_answer": "Very bad quality (red light, oil change asap)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Bad quality (amber light, oil change advised)",
        "Good quality (yellow light)",
        "Bad quality (red light, oil change in a week)"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the tempering of grill chicken?",
      "correct_answer": "24 hours defrost in chiller then 72 hours.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "24 hours defrost in chiller then 24 hours.",
        "24 hours defrost in chiller then 48 hours.",
        "12 hours defrost in chiller then 36 hours."
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What are the inner packages of french fries?",
      "correct_answer": "6 x 2.5kg",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "5 X 2.5kg",
        "4 x 2.5kg",
        "10 x 3kg"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What are the inner packages of twisty fries?",
      "correct_answer": "4 X 2.5kg",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "7 X 2.5kg",
        "3 x 2kg",
        "5 X 2.5kg"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What are the inner packages of shortening?",
      "correct_answer": "2 x 10L",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "3 X 10L",
        "1 X 20L",
        "2 X 5L"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the minimum shelf life on delivery for french fries?",
      "correct_answer": "2 months",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "3 months",
        "4 months",
        "6 months"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the minimum shelf life on delivery for twisty fries?",
      "correct_answer": "6 months",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "5 months",
        "7 months",
        "4 months"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the minimum shelf life on delivery for shortening?",
      "correct_answer": "4 months",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2 months",
        "5 months",
        "8 months"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the tempering of donuts?",
      "correct_answer": "24 hours included 3 hours defrosting.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "24 hours included 2 hours defrosting.",
        "48 hours included 3 hours defrosting.",
        "36 hours included 1 hour warm up."
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What are the inner packages for donuts?",
      "correct_answer": "3 x 24",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "3 x 12",
        "2 x 24",
        "2 x 48"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the minimum shelf life on delivery for donuts?",
      "correct_answer": "90 days",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "72 days",
        "80 days",
        "42 days"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the minimum shelf life on delivery for apple pies?",
      "correct_answer": "42 days",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "90 days",
        "45 days",
        "30 days"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the tempering for desserts?",
      "correct_answer": "5 days unopened included 2 hours defrost.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "3 days unopened included 2 hours defrost.",
        "5 days unopened included 3 hours defrost.",
        "2 days unopened included 1 hour defrost."
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the minimum shelf life on delivery for desserts?",
      "correct_answer": "90 days",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "80 days",
        "20 days",
        "75 days"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What are the inner packages for apple pies?",
      "correct_answer": "7 x20",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "9 x 20",
        "10 x 20",
        "3 x 24"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What are the inner packages of sweet muffins?",
      "correct_answer": "56",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "48",
        "140",
        "72"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What are the inner packages for cookies?",
      "correct_answer": "48",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "74",
        "56",
        "38"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the draw temperature of cold drinks?",
      "correct_answer": "0.1-4째C",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1-4째C",
        "2-4째C",
        "0.1-2째C"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the size of small cold drink?",
      "correct_answer": "250mls",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "200mls",
        "300mls",
        "325mls"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the size of medium cold drink?",
      "correct_answer": "400mls",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "500mls",
        "250mls",
        "425mls"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the size of large drink?",
      "correct_answer": "500mls",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "425mls",
        "325mls",
        "450mls"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the size of medium frappe drink?",
      "correct_answer": "325mls",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "425mls",
        "400mls",
        "250mls"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "McDonald's",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is the size of large frappe drink?",
      "correct_answer": "425mls",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "300mls",
        "450mls",
        "500mls"
      ]
    }
	]
}
